<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<!-- This document was created with Syntext Serna Free. -->
<ConfigurationSettings>
  <EMailInformation>
    <Subject>Welcome to @BRAND_NAME@!</Subject>
    <Message><![CDATA[ <div style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 12px;"> Hi @FIRST_NAME@,<br /> <br /> Your @BRAND_NAME@ account has been activated and is ready for use. Below are the login credentials for your account:<br /> <br /> User ID : @USER_NAME_OR_USER_CODE@<br /> Password : @PASSWORD@<br /> <br /> The password you have been assigned is temporary, and you will be asked to change it during your first login. You may also change your User ID one time.<br /> <br /> <B><u>Setup:</u></B><br /> <br /> Your account was set up to process credit card transactions on most Apple and Android Mobile devices. Please follow the simple steps below to set up your device within minutes:<br /> <br /> 1. Download the @BRAND_NAME@ application from the Apple App Store if you are using an iPhone/iPad/iPod device, or from Google Play if you are using an Android device.<br /> <br /> 2. Log into the @BRAND_NAME@ App with the credentials above and reset your password.<br /> <br /> You are now ready to accept credit cards on your mobile device with @BRAND_NAME@.<br /> <br /><B><u>Swiping Cards:</u></B><br /> <br /> After logging in, please go to the Settings menu, select Card Readers and choose your card swipe device. If you are using a Bluetooth Printer/Reader, please make sure the printer is first paired with your mobile device before starting the mobile payment app.<br /> <br /> <B><u>Web Portal for your @BRAND_NAME@ Account:</u></B><br /> <br /> You can manage your @BRAND_NAME@ account on the web at @COMPANY_URL@. The login credentials for the web portal are the same as the credentials for the mobile device.<br /> <br /> If you have any questions regarding your @BRAND_NAME@ account, or if you need any additional assistance, please contact our Customer Care Team at @COMPANY_SUPPORT_EMAIL@ or @COMPANY_SUPPORT_PHONE@.<br /> <br /> Sincerely,<br /><br /> @BRAND_NAME@ <br/> <!-- @COMPANY_URL@ <br/> --> Contact Sales at: @COMPANY_SALES_EMAIL@, or @COMPANY_SALES_PHONE@ <br/> Contact Support at: @COMPANY_SUPPORT_EMAIL@ or @COMPANY_SUPPORT_PHONE@ <br/> <p style="font-size: 10px;"> <U>Disclaimer and Confidentiality Notice</U>: Please do not reply to this email. This is a system generated email. The information contained in this message intended for the addressee is confidential and may constitute inside or non-public information. If you are not the addressee, please promptly delete this message and notify the sender. </p> </div> ]]></Message>
  </EMailInformation>
</ConfigurationSettings>
