<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ConfigurationSettings>
  <EMailInformation>
    <Subject>Your FocusPay User Credentials</Subject>
    <Message>
      <![CDATA[
      <div style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 12px;">
        Dear @FIRST_NAME@,<br />
        <br />
        Please find the login credentials of your @BRAND_NAME@ account. To login to your
        account, please use the following link:
        <br />
        @COMPANY_URL@<br />
        <br />
        In case of any problems to open the link, please copy the url and paste it in a new browser window.<br />
        <br />
        User ID  : @USER_NAME_OR_USER_CODE@<br />
        Password : @PASSWORD@<br />
        <br />
        You have ONE TIME option to change your User ID using the management portal or the POS.<br />
        <br />
        We recommend following password management guidelines to ensure secure transactions.     
        <pre style="line-height: 1.6em;">
    1.You will be forced to change password immediately after the first use.
    2.Change password at least every @FORCE_CHANGE_PASSWORD@ days.
    3.Require a minimum password length of at least @MIN_PASSWORD_LENGTH@ characters.
    4.Use password containing both numeric and alphabetic characters.
    5.Password cannot be same as any of the last @SAME_PASSWORD_USAGE@ passwords used.
    6.Consecutive @INVALID_PASSWORD_ATTEMPTS@ failure attempts to login shall LOCK OUT the user. User can try login after @LOCKOUT_TIME@ mins or contact administrator.
    7.Session shall expire after @SESSION_TIMEOUT@ minutes. The user is required to re-enter the password to re-activate the session.
    8.Your account will be disabled if left inactive for over @USER_INACTIVE_DAYS@ days.
    9.Do not use group, shared or generic accounts and passwords.</pre>        
        Any questions regarding the use of @BRAND_NAME@ account or if you need any additional
        assistance, please contact support.<br />
        <br />
        Thank you again for choosing @BRAND_NAME@. We are committed to a long and fruitful
        business relationship.
        <br />
        <br />
        Sincerely,<br /><br />
        @BRAND_NAME@<br />        
        Contact Sales at : @COMPANY_SALES_EMAIL@,@COMPANY_SALES_PHONE@<br />
        Contact Support at : @COMPANY_SUPPORT_EMAIL@,@COMPANY_SUPPORT_PHONE@<br />        
        <br />
        <p style="font-size: 10px;">
            Disclaimer and Confidentiality Notice: Please do not reply to this email. This is a system generated email. The information
            contained in this message intended for the addressee is confidential and may constitute
            inside or non-public information. If you are not the addressee, please promptly
            delete this message and notify the sender.
        </p>
    </div>
      ]]>

    </Message>
  </EMailInformation>
</ConfigurationSettings>